Pei Ning.
You really
didn't disappoint me.
Pei Ning,
are you done playing?
Brother.
Do you think
I'm playing?
Pei Ning.
Xiaoning.
The AI system you developed
is not yet perfect.
It still has many security vulnerabilities.
Tell me,
I can help you.
This is your idea.
No one will take it away.
Enough.
There are two bottles of wine on the table.
You choose one.
The old rules.
Arm wrestling after drinking.
As long as you win against me,
I will terminate the program upload.
What if it's poisoned?
I trust Xiaoning.
I keep my word.
Brother.
This is the last time.
Come on.
Go!
Come on!
Xiaoning.
What's wrong?
Brother.
You won again.
Xiaoning!
Are you okay?
What's wrong with you?
His cup was poisoned.
Why?
Xiaoning,
why did you do this?
Why?
You know what?
Since childhood,
I've admired you so much.
I actually don't like math at all.
But because you like it,
I have to like it too.
You like riding motorcycles,
so I have to learn even if I break my legs.
You majored in computer science,
so I have to, too.
You like outdoor sports,
so I have to learn.
I'm just afraid that if I can't keep up with you,
you will leave me behind.
I won't.
I won't, Xiaoning.
It's okay.
But...
No matter what I do,
I can never do as well as you.
Why am I always worse than you?
That's not true, Xiaoning.
It's
my fault for neglecting you.
I'm so tired.
Brother.
You know what?
I really envy the way Shiya looks at you.
That is the gentleness
I've never seen before.
So,
I actually know
that my AI system
has many problems.
But it's all I have.
It's all I have.
I ignored your feelings.
I only have it now.
I'll take you to the hospital.
Xiaoning.
Let's go.
Xiaoning!
Xiaoning,
what are you doing?
Open the door!
Brother,
it's no use.
The programs in the server
will be used by criminals.
Xiaoning!
The server must be destroyed.
Xiaoning,
don't do anything stupid.
The police are on their way!
Shiya,
take my brother away.
It's nice to meet you.
Pei Ning.
In the future,
be happy.
Be happy.
Xiaoning!
Open the door!
You were just used.
I'll go with you to turn yourself in.
Open the door!
Xiaoning!
Open the door.
Xiaoning.
Don't do anything stupid.
Open the door.
Let's go.
Xiaoning.
Pei Song.
Brother.
Great.
Xiaoning,
you're fine.
Brother, what's wrong?
Brother.
I wrote a program during class.
Can you take a look for me?
Okay.
This one.
You don't even know something this simple?
You put this here,
and isn't it done?
Try it.
Right.
Brother, how are you so smart?
No one will walk with you for a lifetime.
Many paths,
even most of them.
We all need to move forward alone.
We may be alone,
but as long as there is love in our hearts,
we will not feel lonely.
But brother,
whether life is a comedy or a tragedy,
the courage to face it
is the meaning of being alive.
True heroism
is that after knowing the truth,
you still choose to remain steadfast.
Song Shiya.
Are you calling me?
Hello.
I'm Pei Song.